To validate the product, you move fast.
You don't have to have the product in stock.
The way we validate products,
let's say, okay,
have this, like,
crazy idea. We want to test,
like, a new product.
What we do is to just validate that demand initially.
We just ordering the product from Amazon,
like, 2,
3 days, boom,
it's delivered. We slapping our logo on it,
we just printing, like,
a sticker. Boom, done.
We're shooting some content with it.
We just finding a semester.
To validate the product, you move fast.
You don't have to have the product in stock.
You know that, like,
if the product sells and if the margin makes sense,
then you'll be able to source.
The biggest part is, like,
actually validating it.
One of the reasons why taking content from TikTok
and passing it on Facebook,
it didn't work,
it could be because of Facebook has very good content detection system.
So if they see that the content is stolen,
they detect it. They kind of suppress the traffic for it.
So Facebook really appreciates the uniqueness of the content.